gluecklicher-tag.com 2017-12-01

# DVX Interactive: Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Updated: November 4, 2016**

DVX LLC ("we" or "us") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out how we process your personal data and your rights in respect of that data.

The data controller is DVX LLC, PO Box 244090, Atlanta, GA 30324, USA

**1\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:  
Information that you provide by filling in any forms on our sites or any others that we own and may from time to time use to collect data ("our site") or when otherwise contacting us; if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence; details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfillment of your orders; details of your visits to our site and the resources that you access.

You should be aware that this site is not intended for, or designed to attract, individuals under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is an individual under the age of 18.

**2\. USE OF COOKIES AND IP ADDRESSES**

DVX is committed to your privacy and keeping you fully informed as to how we implement and use cookies on our web properties.

A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored on a computer for the purpose of identifying that browser during interaction on websites. Cookies may be used to store items such as identifiers and user preferences. A website may set a cookie to the browser if the browser's preferences allow it. A browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has set, not those set by other websites.

We place a transactional cookie on your computer when you arrive at our prize draw websites. This allows us to report a customer visit to our marketing partners and also allows us to track users to monitor for fraud; however, this cookie does not track or identify any individual user, and expire in 24 hours. These cookies do not track your visits to websites other than Lucky Day properties or your overall web usage in any way. You can set your browser to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you do this you may be unable to enjoy full use of the site and you may not be able to take advantage of certain promotions we may run from time to time. Please note that entities who advertise on our site may also use cookies, but we do not have access to them or control over them.

We also may collect information about your computer without the use of cookies (including, where available, your IP address, operating system, and browser type) for system administration, security purposes, and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**3\. USES WE MAY MAKE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:  

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * To provide you with information, products, services or offers via e-mail, SMS, phone or post, that you request from us or which we feel may interest you;
  * Depending on what Personal Information we hold about you, DVX or a Third Party may contact you by post email, telephone, mobile, SMS and MMS text message for direct marketing, debt collection and tracing; or with marketing messages within these and other verticals:  

    * Astrology
    * Gambling
    * Subscription Services
    * Charitable Organisations
    * General Retailers
    * Mobile Telecommunication
    * Comparison Websites
    * Household Goods and Services
    * Travel and Leisure Pursuits
    * Competition Sites
    * Insurance Providers
    * Electric, Gas, Water and Multi-Utilities
    * Debt Collection
    * Personal Injury
    * General Marketing
    * Financial Providers
    * Shares
    * Tracing Activities
    * Fashion and Leisure Goods
    * Health and Welfare
    * Food and Drink Producers and Retailers
  * To confirm the accuracy of the information that we hold about you via third party providers of such services, to include phone, e-mail and postal verification methods;
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

**4\. PASSING YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**

We may sell your data (or otherwise pass it on) to carefully selected third parties who may use it to contact you in relation to offers which we feel may interest you. DVX carefully selects these partners to ensure they comply with Privacy Shield Priciples, and may be liable if third parties do not comply with Priciples. (Principle 7d.)

If you do not want us to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please ensure that you do not give your consent via the relevant boxes situated on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form). You may also email us at info@dvxinteractive.com to request to be opted out from future third-party marketing efforts.

Save where you have given your consent, we do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers. However, we may provide them with aggregate, generalized information about our users.

**5\. OPTING OUT**

If you do not wish us to contact you for marketing purposes, please send an e-mail to info@dvxinteractive.com.

If you do not wish us to pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes, please send an e-mail to us at info@dvxinteractive.com.

**6\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:  
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;

If DVX LLC or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply any of our terms and conditions.

**7\. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to third party websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own terms and privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these sites and their terms and policies.

**8\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you is transferred to, stored at and processed at our secure data center, which may be outside the country in which you reside (including the European Economic Area ("EEA"), Australia, Canada, or the United States). DVX adheres to best practices in the storage of your personal data. By submitting your personal data, you agree to the transfer, storage and processing of any data provided to DVX (or, its partners).

EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Statement: DVX complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. DVX, LLC has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

This organization is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). Please note our organization is required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements 

DVX, LLC commits to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by the panel with regard to data transferred from the EU. You may contact them if you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint.

Although we take every available measure to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of personally identifiable data transmitted to our site, and any transmission is at your own risk.

**9\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

You have the right to access information held about you. Please email us at info@dvxinteractive.com for this information.

**10\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

**11\. CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@dvxinteractive.com or may be mailed to the following address:

DVX Interactive   
PO Box 244090   
Atlanta, GA 30324 USA 

© DVX LLC 2016
